Atlas 2 – Wave layer attribute heading key and descriptions

Timescales

An = Annual
SP = Spring
SU = Summer
AU = Autumn
WI = Winter

JA = January
FB = February
MR = March
AP = April
MY = May
JN = June
JL = July
AG = August
SE = September
OC = October
NV = November
DC = December


Parameters

mean_hs or HSM = Mean Significant Wave Height recorded in metres

mn_P_OD or WPM_OD = Mean Wave Power (Full Wave Field) calculated in kilowatts per metre (kW/m) per horizontal metre of wave crest using the energy period calculation (TE)


Additional Fields (Attribute Heading: Description: Unit)

FID: Internal ArcGIS ID: N/A

Shape: Internal ArcGIS polygon geometry storage: N/A

ID: Renewable Atlas Tidal Cell ID: Integer

Base: Source Met Office model for the cell data: Either ‘UK ‘or ‘Global’

Model_ID: Met Office model Cell ID: Integer

MinDist: Distance of the model cell to closest landfall: Kilometres

Lat: Latitude of the model cell centre: Decimal degrees relative to WGS 84

Long_: Longitude of the model cell centre: Decimal degrees relative to WGS 84

Ave_Depth: Average depth of the model cell: Metres relative to Mean Sea Level
